imajize.com 2015-10-06

# Privacy Policy — Imajize

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, email address, company website. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

· To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

· To send periodic e-mails

The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order and/or account.

Providing us with your email address will not automatically opt you in for our mailing list.

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to opt out of our mailing list, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### Do we use cookies?

Our software that displays product images may use a cookie to determine if a visitor is a first-time visitor or return-visitor. If the cookie determines the visitor is a first-time visitor, then the software will display an instructional message that helps the visitor understand the software’s features. If the cookie determines the visitor is a return- visitor, then the software will not display the instructional message because the visitor has already read it. We do not use cookies for any other purpose.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at www.imajize.com/terms-of- use.html

### Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

### Contacting us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us by visiting the contact page of our website:  
www.imajize.com/support
